# ANURAG PANDEY

#### **SPECIALIST**

#### CONTACT

9650212438

Anuragpandey00786@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

A self-Motivated person with 5 years of experience in Intune&SCCM with ability to work with a big organization on a challenging position to get an opportunity to work on state of art information technologies and achieve new landmarks in career with lot of room for professional advancements.

#### **SKILLS**

Intune\*\*\*\*

SCCM\*\*\*\*

Citrix\*\*

Active directory\*\*\*

### **EDUCATION**

Delhi University

2017-2020

B.com Program SOL.

CO ED Sr Sec School

2015-2016

12<sup>th</sup>

CO ED Sr Sec School

2013-2014

10<sup>th</sup>

#### **EXPERIENCE**

HCL Technologies. (Specialist)

#### 2019-2024

Intune.

- Autopilot & Co-managed
- Enrolling devices to Intune and setup OOBE and ESP page.
- LOB-Win32 app creation deployment management.
- Reporting & Troubleshooting.
- WUFB and reporting.
- Configuration profile creation.
- Compliance policy creation.
- App protection policy creation.
- Vulnerability remediation.

#### SCCM

- OS patching
- Application creation and deployment
- OS troubleshooting & App troubleshooting.
- SQL reporting
- Client upgradation
- Console upgradation
- Boundary cleanup
- Vulnerability remediation.

Convergys Pvt Ltd (Technical support-II)

#### 2018-2019

- GAM work. User creation/Email creation
- Assigning license as per users' role
- Distribution list and shared mailbox creation.

• Call support and remote help.

Tec genome consulting Pvt Ltd. (Back-office associate)

## 2016-2018

- Provide support to UK based users via call.
- Booking users test and course slots online to get license to work at construction site.